The bond market is starting to revolt,
the Fed's not raising rates, and if this
plays out like either 2023 or 2022 or
2018 or 2014, then you'd be looking at a
correction coming up in the latter part
of Q3. So, it made sense to say that
look, we were going to form a low by
late June, early July. We did.
Countertrend rally in July, check. Could
it extend a little bit into August? It
could. But, I would guess that we'll see
um Bitcoin come back down as we get
later on uh into the month of August,
and and notably September. What's
remarkable is when you look at the
monthly returns of Bitcoin in mid-term
years, July is often green, but look at
2022, July was green, and then August,
September, red. 2018, July was green,
August, September, red.
Even in 2014 when July was red, August
and September were still red.